A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Documents of Record, SG 16.4 FA1314
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, Documents of Record, SG 16.4
1913-1988
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA1314
8.25 Cubic Feet 18 letter document boxes, 3 legal document boxes.
Arrangement
Chronological.
Scope and Contents
Contains documents of record.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 20 years old are open for research.
- Documents of Record, Vol. 1, 1913-1914 (Box 1)
- Documents of Record, Vol. 2-3, 1915-1916 (Box 2)
- Documents of Record, Vol. 4, 1917 (Box 3)
- Documents of Record, Vol. 5-6, 1918-1919 (Box 4)
- Documents of Record, Vol. 7-9, 1920-1922 (Box 5)
- Documents of Record, Vol. 10-12, 1923-1925 (Box 6)
- Documents of Record, Vol. 13-17, 1926-1930 (Box 7)
- Documents of Record, Vol. 18-20, 1931-1934 (Box 8)
- Documents of Record, Vol. 21-22, 1935-1936 (Box 9)
- Documents of Record, Vol. 23-24, 1937-1939 (Box 10)
- Documents of Record, Vol. 25-26, 1940-1943 (Box 11)
- Documents of Record, Vol. 27-28, 1944-1947 (Box 12)
- Documents of Record, Vol. 29-30, 1948-1951 (Box 13)
- Documents of Record, Vol. 31-32, 1952-1955 (Box 14)
- Documents of Record, Vol. 33-34, 1956-1959 (Box 15)
- Documents of Record, Vol. 35-36, 1960-1963 (Box 16)
- Documents of Record, Vol. 37-38, 1964-1970 (Box 17)
- Documents of Record, 1,108-1,205, 1970-1978 (Box 18)
- Documents of Record, 1,119-1,150, 1971-1973 (Box 19)
- Documents of Records, 1,151-1,247, 1974-1983 (Box 20)
- Documents of Record, 1,206-1,247, 1979-1984 (Box 19)
- Documents of Record, Index, 1913-1984 (Box 21)
- Documents of Record, 1,248-1,286, 1984-1988 (Box 21)